National Council for the Traditional Arts (NCTA) collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Performer and Genre Lists
  - Genres
Alison Krauss & Union Station
Alleghany Moon
Allen, Joshua
Allen-Lilly Band
Alleuve, Obanila
Allison, Bernard
Alonso, Sergio
Alred, Rick
AltaiKAI
Altan
Ambegaokar, Anjani
American Folk Festival cast
American Gospel Traditions
American Indian Dance Theatre
American Indian Music & Dance Troupe
American Indian Music and Dance Troupe
American Indian Percussion Ensemble
American Piano Masters
American Swedish Spelmans Trio, The
Ana Vinagre & Friends
Ana Vinagre, Manuel Leite and Alvaro Medeiros
Anacostia High Concert Choir
Anderson, Celestine
Anderson, Gerald
Anderson, Kathy
Anderson, Scotty
Anderson, Virgil
Anderson-Troxell Family Reunion
Andrade, Heidi
Andrei Pidkivka & Gheorghe Trambitas
Andrews, Ben
Andy M. Stewart and Gerry O'Beirne
Andy McGann, Brian Conway, Patrick Mangan, Felix D
Andy Statman Klezmer Trio
Angels (U.H.O.P.) Shout Band, The
Angkor Dance Troupe
Anglo And Irish Balladry
Ann Yao & Lu Peng
Announcer
Anthracite Miners
Apache Indian Dancers, The
Milt and Laura Appleby and Joe Pomerleau
Applejack
Arab Dancers
Arabic Music Workshop
Aravod Ensemble
Archuleta, Eppie
Ardoin Family Band
Ardoin Family Band with Canray Fontenot
Ardoin, Alphonse "Bois Sec"
Ardoin, Alphonse "Bois Sec" and Canray Fontenot
Ardoin, Chris
Ardoin, Dexter
Ardoins
Armstrong Twins, The
Armstrong, Howard
Arntzen, Eldrid Skjold
Arsenault, Louise
Art Galbraith and Gordon McCann
Arthur Hall Afro American Dance Ensemble
Ashby, John
Asian American Arts Center
At The Country Fair
Aucella, Peter
Auctioneering Styles
Audience Members
Austrian Student Goodwill Tour
Avilés, Celestino
Ayala, Pedro
Ayryan Ensemble
Herawi, Aziz
Back Step
Bad Luck Songs Workshop
Badgette Sisters
Badlands Singers
Bahamas Junkanoo Revue
Bahamas Junkanoo Revue-2001
Baker, Etta
Baker, Kenny
Balalaika Trio
Balfa Brothers
Balfa, Dewey
Balfa, Dewey 1991
Balkan Four, The
Ball, E.C
Ball, E.C. and Orna
Ball, E.C. and Orna w/Carol Henderson and Bobby Montgomery
Ball, Marcia
Ballard Branch Bogtrotters
Ballog, Tony
Ballog, Tony
Baltimore All-Stars Céilí Band
Balys, Dr. Jonas
Banja Luka
Banjo Roots w/Seeger, Swingle, Ayers & Hester
Bannerman Family and Highwoods String Band
Bannerman Family Mountain Cloggers
Bannerman, Glenn and Family
Barachois
Barbee Brothers, The
Barbee/Bice Family, The
Bardezbanian, Alan Shavarsh
Barnes, Bobby
Barr Family and Tony Ellis
Barr Family, The
Barr Family, The 1995 BRP
Barr, Stevie
Barr, Tom
Barsamian, Mal
Bartenstein, Fred
Barthé, Earl
Bartlett, Jon
Bashell, Louis
Basque Bertsolari
Bass, Fontella
Bass, Howard
Baston, Bruce
Batoon, Maria
Batyi, George
Beacons, The
Beacons, The 1998 NFF
Beale Street Jug Band
Bear, Joyce
Beaton, Andrea
Beau Jocque & The Zydeco Hi-Rollers
Beaudoin Family, The
Beaudoin Project
Beaudoin, Louis
BeauSoleil avec Michael Doucet
Beausoleil Lowell 1989
Beausoliel
Beers, Bob and Evelyne
Beginish
Beier, Ludo vic
Bel Sandré
Belfour, Robert
Bell, Earl
Bell, Janine
Bell, Leon
Bellanger, Agnes
Bellar, Johnny
Ben Guillemette and Friends
Benard, Gaston
Benard, Gaston
Bennet, Gary
Bennett, Earnest
Bennett, Sue
Benson, Mozell
Benson, Steve
Benton Flippen And The Smokey Valley Boys
Beolach
Bergeniova, Beata
Bergey, Barry
Bergey, Jane
Bermejo, Mili
Bernier, Rich
Best, Carroll
Betts, Keter
LaVette, Bettye
Bich Nga Burrill
Biegaj, Eddie
Big Chief Monk Boudreaux & the Golden Eagles
Big Country Bluegrass
Big Ed Thompson and the All Stars
Big River Boys, The
Biggins, Kathleen
Bijela Zvijezda
Bilides, Sophia
Bill Bevic Orchestra, The
Bill Kirchen & Too Much Fun
Bill Neely and Larry Kirbo
Billington, James Hadley
Bilyeu, Tom
Birchfield, Ethyl
Black And White Roots
Black Diamond
Black Twig Pickers
Black, M.
Blake, George
Blake, John
Blake, Norman and Nancy
Blanchard, Pierre
Blankenship, Spencer
Blaylock Brothers
Blevins, Haywood "Woody"
Blind Boys of Alabama
Blind Boys of Alabama featuring Clarence Fountain
Blinky & the Roadmasters
Blinky and the Roadmasters
Blizard, Ralph
Blodgett, John
Bloom, Jim
Blue Highway
Blue Legs, Alice New Holy
Blue Ridge
Blue Ridge All-Stars
Blue Ridge Mountain Band
Blue Ridge Mountain Dancers
Blue Ridge Mountain String Band
Bluegrass Alliance
Bluegrass Band, The
Bluegrass Brothers
Bluegrass Mountaineers, The
Bluegrass Tradition Band
The Bluzblasters with Frankie Lee
Boardman & Sons
Bob French's Original Tuxedo Jazz Band
Bob Holt and the Douglas County Dancers with H.K. Silvey and Alvie Dooms
Bobby Parker Band
Bogan, Ted
Boldán III, José Maria
Boldán, José Maria
Bomba y plena Workshop
Bommelyn, Loren
Bonane, Wawali
Bond, Eddie
Boorgerhoff, Beth
Borderline
Borque, Benoit
Boston CCE Ceili Band
Boston Chinese Youth Dulcimer
Boston Edge
Boston, Richard
Boukman Eksperyans
Bourisaw, Aloysius "Bouse"
Bourne, Dave
Bourque, Benoit
Bowers, Bryan
Bowman, Barbara
Bowman, Richard
Boyd, Shane
Boyer, Claude
Boyer, Horace
Boyer, Pete
Boys Of The Lough
BR5-49
Bradley, Dale Ann
Bradley, Fred
Bradley, Sandy
Branch, Jack
Brasileirinho 1994 LFF
Brave Old World
Braymer, Betty
Breau, Denny
Breaux, Jimmy
Brendan Callahan, Jim Eagan, Elliot Grasso, Margot
Brendan McGlinchey & Nigel Stevens
Brendan McGlinchey, Patrick Mangan & Nigel Stevens
Brendan McGlinchey, Roger Sherlock & Nigel Stevens
Brendan Mulvihill and Brian Gaffney
Brendan Mulvihill and Donna Long
Bresnick-Perry, Roslyn
Brewster, Jamesie
Brian Glynn & Company
Brian Marshall and the Tex-Slavic Playboys
Bright, Flecther
Brisendine, Everett
Bromberg, David
Bromberg, David (NFF 1974)
Bronx New Heaven Shout Band
Brose, David
Brother Style Songs
Brotherhood Gospel Choir 1994 NFF
Broto Roy & Debi Prasad Chatterjee
Broto Roy Trio
Broudy, Saul
Browe, Denny
Brown, Charles
Brown, Chuck
Brown, Clarence "Gatemouth"
Brown, Erica
Brown, Junior
Brown, Paul
Brown's Chapel Choir
Bruce Daigrepont Cajun Band
Vin Bruce and the Acadians
Bruce, W. Guy
Brunet, André
Bruno, Hal
Brush School
Bruso, Nora Jean
Brzozowska, Phyllis
Buckingham Lining Bar Gang
Buckley, Fiona Dore
Bud and Jonita Hunt
Bud Hundenski and the Corsairs
Bulger, Brendan
Bulger, Peggy
Buller, Becky
Bullock Brothers, The
Bullshooting Workshop
Bun, Em
Burke Family, The
Burke, Kevin
Burkhart, Samuel
Burlison, Paul
Burlison, Tex
Burnin' The Rosin
Burnside, R.L. & The Sound Machine
Burris, J.C.
Burton, James
Bushyhead, Eddie
Buster B. Jones & Brooks E. Robertson
Butler Twins Blues Band
Butler, Edith
Butler, Henry
Byrd, Senator Robert Byrd
C.J. Chenier And His Red Hot Louisiana Band
Cables, Herb
Cage, Bob
Calabria Bella
Calico
Calvert, Ward
Calvin Cooke Sacred Steel Ensemble
Camaera
Cambodian Dancers
Cambodian-American Heritage Music and Dance Troupe
Camp, Charlie
Campa, Dr. Arthur L.
Campbell Brothers
Campbell, Charles "Chuck"
Campbell, Dr. Charles
Cana Ramblers
Cannon, Hal
Cano, Nati y Los Camperos
Cano, Natividad
Cantaneo, Angelo and Margarita
Canterbury Orchestra
Canterbury Orchestra And Dancers (NFF 1974)
Cape Breton Music and Dance
Cape Breton Square Sets
Capercaillie
Capoeira Angola
Capoeira Camara
Cara Butler and Donny Golden
Carawan, Guy
Carl Sauceman and the Green Valley Boys
Carl Tipton Show, The
Carlos de Leon Orchestra
Carnes, Barbara
Carnival Traditions Workshop
Carpenter, Mary Chapin
Carrillo, Charles M.
Carroll, Liz
Carter and Addington Families
Carter Family Band
Carter Family Tribute Band from Crooked Road Tour
Carter, Janette
Carter, Jason
Casey, Karan
Casey, Marion R.
Cashdollar, Cindy
Caspal Group
Matteo Casserino and Gino DiMichele
Castaneda, Edmar
Castellanoz, Genoveva
Catala, Luis; Ernestina Reyes and Musicians
Catalon, Inez
Catch the Fire
Catholic Central High School
Causeway
Ceilidh House
Celedonio Alvarez and Marcelina Valencia
Celia Ayala y su Ballet 1993 LFF
Cellicion Family Zuni Singers, The
Cellicion Traditional Zuni Singers, The
Celtic Thunder
Cephas and Wiggins
Cephas, John
Cervante, Tony ‘El Chayos'
Chadwick, Alex
Chaksam-pa
Chamberlain, Oliver
Chang, Grace
Chanthraphone, Bounxou
Charivari
Charlebois, Jeanne d'Arc
chat
Chatmon, Sam
Chatuye
Chavez, Alex
Chávez, Carlos
Chavis, Boozoo & The Majic Sounds 1994 LFF
Chavis, Boozoo & The Majic Sounds 1994 NFF
Chavis, Wilson "Boozoo"
Diabete, Cheick Hamala
Chenier, Clifton
Cheremosh
Cherish The Ladies
Cherokee Indian Baptist Choir
Chief Ellis and Brownie McGee
Chief Ellis and Mike Stewart
Chief Jake Millon and the Mardi Gras Indians
Children's Songs and Games
Childs, Bob
Chinese Lion & Dragon Dancers 1994 NFF
Chinese Opera Society
Choiniere, Michele
Chosen Sisters
Chris Ardoin and Double Clutchin'
Christenson, Betty Pisio
Christian Harmony
Chulrua
Chuna McIntyre & Nunamta
Chuna McIntyre w/Marie Meade, Josephine Aloralrea
Churchill, Dolores E.
Cimeara with Jillian Boucher
Cindy Cashdollar & Elana James
Cissoko, Ali
Claire Lynch & the Front Porch String Band
Brown, Clarence "Gatemouth"
Clarence "Gatemouth" Brown 1997
Clarence Fountain & the Five Blind Boys of Alabama
Clarence Thompson, Sr. & The New Spirits
Clark Octa & Hector Duhon
Clark, Jewell
Clark, Mickey
Claude Williams Trio
Claude Williams Trio & Jimmy Slyde
Claude Williams Trio
Clayton, Bob
Cleaver, Marshall
Cleveland Irish Musicians, The
Cleveland, Michael
Cliff, Mary
Clifton, Bill
Clint Howard, Fred Price & Sons
Clotet, Hector
Clyde Davenport, Willard Anderson and Bobby Fulcher
Clyde Sproat and Karin Haleamau
Coast to Coast Country Guitar Traditions
Cochiti Indian Dancers, The
Cockburn, Bruce
Coen, Father Charlie
Coen, Jack
Coggins, Matt
Cohen, Andy
Cohen, Dave
Cole, Robert
Collier, Roosevelt
Collin, Aurelle
Collinet, Georges
Collins, Amber
Collins, Cal
Collins, Dan and Kathleen
Colvin, Joe
Coming Together Festival
Congressman Mike Synar
Conjunto Hueyapan
Connell, Dudley
Connie and Barbara
Connolly, Bulger and Murphy
Connolly, Coen, Mulhaire, Dolan
Connolly, Deirdre
Connolly, Seamus
Conte, Pat
Contemporary Greek Ensemble 1993 LFF
Continental Gypsy Strings
Continental Strings
Cook, Bertha
Cooke, Calvin
Cooney, Michael
Cooper, Carson
Cooper, Jonathan
Copeland, Shemekia
Copley Ceili Band
Cora Lee Phillips and Etta Baker
Corbin, Michael
Cormier, J.P.
Cormier, Joe
Cormier, Lesa and the Sundown Playboys
Corn Drinkers, The
Costuming Workshop
Coteau
Cotten, Elizabeth
Cotton Blossom Singers
Country & Western Music Workshop
Country Boys
Country Connection
Courtney Hollow Band
Courville, S.D. and Dennis McGee
Couzman, Jesus
Covington, Freda
Cowan, Carol
Cox, Joey
Craig, Burlon
Crane, Pat
Craobh Rua
Crawford, Kevin
Cree, Rose and Francis
Creed, Kyle
Creed, Kyle and Fred Cockerham
Creed, Kyle with Albert Hash and his band
Creek Nation
Creole Sextet and the Cape Verdean American Folkloric Dance Troupe
Crescendos, The
Croatian Dancers
Crooked Road Oldtime Band
Crowe, J.D.
Crusade Polka Band
Cubanakán
Cuchullan
Cuchullan With Caledonia Set Dancers
Cuchullan With Deirdre Goulding
Cuellar, Jimmy
Cuffe, Tony
Cullinan, Elizabeth
Cumberland And Ozark Gospel (NFF 1979)
Curran, Beth
Curto, Robert
Cyr, Don
Cyril Pahinui & Patrick Landeza
D. Bourne, J. Little, D. Davis
D.C. Aires Gospel Singers
D.C. Country Dance Association Callers Group
D.L. and Larry Menard and Doc Guidry
D.L. Menard w/Terry Huval & the Jambalaya Cajun Band
D.L. Menard, Dewey Balfa and the Louisiana Aces
Dahlin, Paul
Daigle, Paul
Daigrepont, Bruce
Bradley, Dale Ann
Dale Jett
Dale Watson and His Lone Stars
Dallas Chief Eagle
Dalton Roberts And Friends
Dameon
Damessae, Seleshe
Dan Paisley & the Southern Grass
Dance Styles
Dance Styles Demonstration (NFF 1979)
Danforth, Percy
Danoff, Bill
Danú
Daugherty, Junior
Dave Evans and River Bend
Davenport, Clyde
Davenport, Clyde, Willard Anderson and Bobby Fulch
David & Levon Ayriyan
David & Linda Lay
David & Linda Lay w/Sammy Shelor
David Doucet & Scott Fore
Davis, Daryl
Davis, Derek
Dawson, Ronnie
Day, Douglas
De Dannan
Debi Prasad Chatterjee
DeBusk-Weaver Family
Dee and Delta Hicks
Dee, Delta and Lula Mae Hicks
Dee, Ruby
DeFranco, Giuseppe and Raffaela
Del McCoury Band
Delafose, Geno
John Delafose and the Eunice Playboys
Delgado, Miguel
Delton Broussard and Calvin Carrière
Demaris, Mike
Demas, Alex
Demers, Oliver
Denney, Mike
Dennis McGee & Sady Courville
Dennis Polisky and the Maestro's Men
Depression Songs Workshop (NFF 1978)
Derailers, The
Derrane, Joe
Derrane, Joe with Felix Dolan
Dervish
Deseret String Band
Dessens, Bill
Dessesns and Gasaway
DeVane, Dwight
Dewey Balfa and Steve Riley
Dewhurst, Kurt
Dexter Ardoin & the Creole Ramblers
Diabate, Cheik Hamala
Diabate, Mamadou
Diabete, Cheick Hamala
Diaz, Joaquin
Dickens, Hazel
Dickens, Hazel and Alice Gerrard
Dickens, Hazel with Ted Lundy, Bob Paisley and the Southern Mountain Boys
Dickey, Lotus
Dildine Family
Dildine, John
Dinatale, Doug
Diner, Hasia
DinoRock
Dismembered Tennesseans, The
Diunna Greenleaf & Blue Mercy
Dixie Hummingbirds
Djimo Kouyate & Family
Djimo Kouyate And Mamaya
Djoko Pribich Tamburitzans
Dlaikan, Nadim
Doc Paulin And His Dixieland Band
Doc Paulin's Brass Band 1994 LFF
Doc Paulin's Dixieland Band
Doc Paulin's Dixieland Jazz Band
Doc Paulin's New Orleans Brass Band NFF 1993
Docette, Louis
Dodge, Marshall
Domsch, Sonia
Don Reno, Bill Harrell & the Tennessee Cutups
Don Roy Trio
Don Vappie and the Creole Jazz Serenaders
Don Walser And The Pure Texas Band
Donaldson, Sam
Donato Rizza and Luigi Fusco
Donna Long & Jesse Smith
Donna the Buffalo
Doorley
Doorley, Eamonn
Doorley, Tom
Dorado Schmitt & All Star Band
Dorothy Rorick with John Ashby and Reed Martin
Doucet, David
Doucet, Michael
Doucet, Michael
Doucet, Michael 2000 NFF
Doucet/Arrat
Doug Wallin and Frank Proffitt, Jr.
Doug Wallin and Johnny Ray Hicks
Douglas, Bob
Douglas, Jerry
Down Home Gospel
Downtown Poker Club
Doyle Lawson and Quicksilver
Doyle, Danny
Doyle, John
Dr. Ross
Dreadfulwater, Reverend J.B
Dreher, Marko
Driftwood, Jimmy
Dry Branch Fire Squad
Dudley Connell and Don Rigsby
Dundorf, Caryl
Dunlap, Gene
Dunn Family with Robert Stuart
Dunn, Jackie
Dunn, Lloyd
Duo Frenesi
Dupuis, Dominique
Krishnan, Durga
Durga Krishnan & Dancers
Duskin, Big Joe
Dykeman, Wilma
Dyson, Ernest
Earle, Steve
Early, James
Earnest East and the Pine Ridge Boys
East Rome Singing Group
East Side Group
Eastern Band Of Cherokee Dancers
Eastern Sound Orchestra
Ebenezer Baptist Church Choir
Ebenezer Baptist Church Mass Choir
Eberhart, Jonathan
Eberl, Jacob
Echeverria, Patricia Villalobos
Eckhaus, Joel
Ecos de Borinquen
eddie
Eddie & Alonzo Pennington
Eddie Blazonczyk's Versatones
Eddie Bo and Band
Eddie Bond & Kirk Sutphin
Eddie Bond, Kirk Sutphin, Wayne Henderson, Herb Key
Eddie Bushyhead & Eastern Band of Cherokee Indians
Eddie Kamae
Eddie Pennington and Warner Williams
Edith Butler and les Danseurs du St. Laurent
Castaneda, Edmar
Edwards, Archie
Edwards, David "Honeyboy"
Edwin Colón Zayas y Familia Colón
Edwin Colon Zayas Y Su Taller Campesino
Edwin Johnson Swedish Trio
Edwin Ortiz y su Orquesta La Romana
Egan, Seamus
Egan, Seamus & Friends
Egipciaco, Rosa Elena
Eileen Ivers & Friends
Eileen Ivers & Immigrant Soul
Eileen Ivers Band
El Espirtu del Flamenco
Elaine Hoffman Watts
Eldon Williams & Earl Sawyer
Eller Brothers and Ross Brown, The
Eller, Randal
Ellin, David
Ellis Island Irish Band
Ellis, Big Chief
Ellis, Big Chief and John Cephas
Ellis, Big Chief and the Barrelhouse Rockers
Ellis, Bill
Ellis, Eleanor
Ellis, Tony
El-Sagir, Abraham
Elston, Bob
Emanuel, Leonard
Emert Brothers
Emert Brothers, The
Emmanuelle & Pastelle LeBlanc
Engelhard, Henry
English Folk Dance
Enis, Mike and Company
Enloe, Lyman
Eno, Camille
Entourloupe
Epperson, Ralph
Eritage
Ernest East & the Pine Ridge Boys
Errol Verret and Michael Doucet
Ethel Caffie-Austin
Ethel Caffie-Austin Singers
Ethyl Birchfield and Bill Birchfield
Eugene O'Donnell, Mick Moloney and Martin Fahey
Eveready Singers, The
Everhardt, Gary E.
Evolution of the Blues
Exploring American Indian Music
Fabrangen Fiddlers, The
Fabulous Bullock Brothers, The
Fahey, John
Fahlbusch, Albert
Fain, Brian
Fairfield Four
Fanning, Charles
Fantcha
Farlow, Tal
Fast Forward
Father & Son
Favreau, Eric
Fawley, Clarence
Fedoriouk, Alexander
Ferlatte, Diane
Ferreira, Deraldo
Ferrel, Frank
Ferry, Ham
Fescue
Fiddle & Bow
Fiddling Chillicothe Style
Filé
Fink, Edmondson, Jones
Finnish Folk Dancers from Chicago
Firefighters' Emerald Society Pipe Band
First African Baptist Singers
Fisher's Peak Timber Rattlers
Flacke, Ray
Flannery, Ron
Flannery, Ron
Flatfoot, Clog and Buckdance Contest
Flatley, Michael
Flatt & Scruggs
Fletcher Bright & the Dismembered Tennesseans
Fletcher Bright Fiddle Band
Flint Nation Singers
Flippen, Benton and Larry
Florencio Baro & Eri Okan
Floyd, "Harmonica" Frank
Flute & Whistle Workshop
Flute Talk
Flying Other Brothers
Fochabers Fiddlers
Foddrell Brothers
Folk Process
Fontenot, Canray
Ford, Thomas Edison "Brownie"
Fore, Scott
Forge Creek Boys
Forms Of Slide Guitar
Forró for All
Forster, Omer
Fountain, Buzz
Four Eagle Gospel Singers, The
Fox, Phil
Fr. Charlie Coen, Jack Coen & Felix Dolan
Fraley, J.P. and Annadeene
Francisco Ulloa y su Grupo Tipico
Frank Fernandez and Irvan Perez
Frank London's Klezmer Brass Allstars
Frank, Keith
Frank, Rose
Frankie and Doug Quimby
Franklin Mountain Bluegrass Band
Franklin, "Guitar" Pete
Franklin, Mildred
Freeman, Carol
Freeman, Scot
Fremerman, Elana
French Connections: Acadia, Louisiana and Beyond
French Music In America
Frisberg, Jonno
John Fritzler & The Polka Band
Frohnmayer, John
Fujima, Kansuma
Fulcher, Bobby
Full Gospel Quartet/Dean Family
Full Throttle
Fuzzy Mountain String Band
Gaelic Singing Workshop
Gaffney, Brian
Galax Little Leaves
Galbrain, Robin
Galbraith, Art & McCann, Gordon
Gallagher, Steve
Galvin, Kieran
Gamarnik, Vladimir
Gamelan Mitra Kusuma
Ganga
Garden, Olen
Gardner, Eldon
Garnier III, D'Jalma
Garvey, Willum and Robbie O'Connell
Sredzienski, Gary
Gaupasa and the Oinkari Basque Dancers
Gaylord Klancik Orchestra
Ge Xiong and His Students
Gealbháin, Ciarán
Gellert, Dan
Geno Delafose & French Rockin' Boogie
George, Delores
Georgia On My Mind
Gerald Anderson & Spencer Strickland
Gerrard, Alice and Mike Seeger
Ghent, Aubrey
Gilles Roy and the Stepping Ambassadors
Gillis Brothers, The
Gimble, Johnny
Gioia, Dana
Git-Hoan Dancers
Glaser, Meg
Glenn Davis and the Buffalo Ford Boys
Glenn Orlin & Pat Richardson
Glosson, Lonnie
Godfrey, Erika
Golden River Grass
Golden Stars
Golden, Barbara
González, Alicia
González, José
Gonzalo Grau y La Clave Secreta
Gordon Tanner and the Jr. Skillet Lickers
Gore, Sr., Senator Albert
Gospel Apprenticeships w/Newsone & Madison Hummingbirds
Gospel Harmonizers
Gospel Jubilators
Gospel Messengers, The
Gospel Songbirds, The
Gospel Workshop/Concert NFF 1992
Gottesman, Beyle Schaechter
Grace and Fire Band
Graham, Len
Grand Master Seiichi Tanaka
Grasso and Mangan
Grasso, Elliot
Grateful Dead
Graves Family, The
Gray, Henry
Gray, Karen
Grayson Highlands Stringband
Grcevich, Jerry
Greely, David
Green Fields of America, The
Green Grass Cloggers
Green, Doug and Jerry
Greenfields of America
Greenleaf, Diunna
Greenman, Steven
Greg Hooven & The Backstep Band
Greg Hooven and the Ballard Branch Bogtrotters
Greg Hooven String Band, The
Gregory and Davenport
Griffin, Patty
Griffith, Jim
Griffith, Nanci
Grise, Dr. George
Grkman, Joe
Groce, Nancy
Groethe, D.W
Groupo Pilon Cola
Growing Up In The Ozarks
Grupo Fantasma
Grupo Folclorico Lusitanos of Fall River
Grupo Latino Continental
Guerrero, Eduardo "Lalo"
Guillemette, Ben
Guitar Masters Cephas & Pessar, Fore & Lunsford
Gujarati Garba Raas 1994 NFF
Gulley, Steve
Gustafson, Wylie
Gutiérrez, José
Gutierrez, Juan
Gutkin, Lisa
Guzevich, Gus
Haberl, Sister Rosalia
Hagopian, Richard
Halata, Mark
Halau Hula O Mililani
Haleamau `Ohana
Haleamau, Karin
Haleamau, Karin and Gary with Clyde Sproat
Halkias, Periklis
Hall, Kenny and the Sweets Mill String Band
Hallelujah Ride
Halsay, Bill
Ham, Audrey Hash
Hammered Dulcimer: Persia & China
Hammond, Lee
Hand, James
Handy, Antoinette
Hank Sapoznik & the Youngers of Zion
Hank Williams Songs from Texas, Louisiana and Tennessee
Hannan, Robbie
Hanson, Morton
Happy Heart Tamburitza Orchestra
Hard Luck Songs Workshop
Hard Times In The Mines
Harmony Echoes, The
Harney, Richard "Hacksaw"
Harold "Chuck" Luce With Nick Hawes
Harold Luce Trio
Harris, Bill
Harris, Emmylou
Harris, Fred
Harris, LaDonna
Hart, E. Richard
Hart, Mickey
Harte, Frank
Hartford, John
Hartwich, Karl
Harvey, Anne-Charlotte
Hascal Haile: Guitar Maker
Hash, Albert and Whitetop Mountain Band
Haslam, Cliff
Hatsegana
Hauter, Sally
Hawaiian Cowboys, The
Hawes, Bess Lomax
Hawes, Nick
Hawkins, Dale
Hawks, Billy
Hayes, Chris
Dickens, Hazel
Heaney, Joe
Heather Berry & the Virginia Carolina Band
Heavenly Tones, The
Hellenic and near Eastern Musical Society
Henderson, Gary
Henderson, Hooven & Sutphin
Henderson, Nyle
Henderson, Wayne
Hengel, Christy
Henny & the Versa J's
Henries, Hawk
Henry and Vernell Townsend
Henry Butler & the Game Band
Henry, Evalena
Henry, Kevin
Herawi, Aziz
Herbert, Donna
Heritage
Herron, Don
Hester, Hoot
Hezekiah and the Houserockers
Hickerson, Joe
Hicks, Dee
Hicks, Delta
Hicks, Johnnie Ray
Hicks, Ray
Hicks, Stanley
High Integrity
Highlanders
Highlanders with Patsy Stoneman
Highwoods String Band
Hillbilly Jam Session 7/28/1991
Hinshaw, Lonnie
Hinson, Glen
Hinton, Algia Mae
Hinton, Holeman, Holloway
Hinton, Sam
Hitchner, Earle
Hmong International Cultural Reunion
Ho'opi'i, Solomon and Richard
Hoaloha
Hocak Wazijaci Singers and Dancers
Hodsoll, Frank
Holeman, John Dee
Holland, Jerry
Holloway, Fris
Holloway, Fris and John Dee Holeman
Holloway, Quentin "Fris"
Holm, Celeste
Holmes Brothers, The
Holmes, Mike
Holt, George
Holtzberg, Maggie
Holtzberg, Maggie
Holum, John
Holy Temple Church of Christ Choir
Holyoak, Van
Honchoettes
Honoring Mick Maloney
Hooked Rug Design
Hooper, Charlene
Hooper, Flo Cody
Hopewell Young Peoples Chorus
Hopkins, Doc
Horace Clarence Boyer and the Year of Jubilee 3
Horan, Winnie
Horejs, Vit
Hornsby. Bruce
Horowitz, Murray
Horton, Abe
Hot 8 Brass Band
Hot Club of Cowtown with Johnny Gimble
Hot Club Of Cowtown, The
Hot Kugel Klezmer Band
Hot Licks Workshop
How To Raise Your Children Right
Howard Armstrong & Friends
Howard, Clint
Howard, Clint and Fred Price
Hula Halau O Kamuela II
Hula Halau o Kealí i o Nalani
Hula Halau 'O Lilinoe
Hula Monsters, The
Hunt, Bud
Hunt, Mrs. Van Zula Carter
Hunter, Janie
Hunter, Marvin
Hurd, Terry
Hutton, Bruce
Huun Huur Tu
Hye Echoes With Susan And Gary Lind-Sinanian, The
Hyman School Singers
I Remember Albert
Ibarra, Sarafin
Ice Band
If It Works It's Right
IIIrd Tyme Out
Inca Son
India Jazz Suites w/ Jason Samuels Smith & Pandit Chitresh Das
Insixiengmai, Khamvong
Iovanne, Tom
Irish Music and Dance: McKennas, Seamus Ennis, Kevin Henry, Mike Flatley
Irish Session with Jesse Smith and Colm Gannon, Mi
Irish Tradition, The w/Mick Moloney
Iroquois Indian Drum Dancers from Buffalo, NY
Iroquois Music and Dance
Iroquois Singers and Dancers
Frank Fernandez and Irvan Perez
Irvin L. Trujillo
Iskwelahang Phlipino Rondalla
Italian And Country Mandolin Styles
Ivan Cuesta Y Sus Baltimore Vallenatos
Ivers, Eileen
Ivey, Bill
Ivo Papasov & Yuri Yunakov
J. D. Crowe & the New South
J.P. Cormier & Friends
Jabbour, Alan
Jack Coen and Friends
Jack Zarzatian Armenian Ensemble
Jackson Family, The
Jackson, George
Jackson, John
Jackson, John and James
Jackson, Nettie
Jackson, Wanda
Jagoda, Flory
James "Son" Thomas and Lewis "Rabbit" Anderson Muse
James Hand & the Magic Band
James Kelly & Daithi Sproule
James Kelly and Zan McLeod
James Kimbrough Band, The
James King Band
James, Elana
James, Jimmie
James, Kathy
Jamesie & The Allstars with Blinky McIntosh
Japanese Traditional Arts
Jaques, Sabin
Jarrell, Tommy
Jason Samuels Smith & Pandit Chitresh Das
Jausoro, Jimmy
Javadov, Rafael
Jeanette Williams and Clearwater
Jeff Little & Friends
Jeff Little & Friends with Scotty Anderson
Jemez Pueblo Buffalo Dancers
Jennings
Douglas, Jerry
Jerry Grcevich & Friends 1993 LFF
Jerry Grcevich Tamburitza Ensemble
Jerry Grcevich Tamburitza Orchestra
Jerry Holland and Friends
Jerry Intihar Orchestra
Jerry McCain With Microwave Dave & The Nukes
Jerry O'Sullivan Trio